Step 1: click (697, 870) [OK]\NI need to make the first chess move by moving the e2 pawn to e4. Looking at the chess board, I can see the white pieces
Step 2: click (700, 870) [OK]\NLooking at the chess board, I can see the white pieces at the bottom (row 1 and 2) and black pieces at the top (row 7 an
Step 3: click (700, 870) [OK]\NLooking at the current chess board, I can see the white pieces at the bottom (rows 1 and 2). The e2 pawn is the white pa
Step 4: click (697, 870) [OK]\NI can see a chess board on the screen. The white pieces are at the bottom (rows 1 and 2), and I need to move the e2 pawn
Step 5: click (697, 870) [OK]\NI can see a chess board on the screen with white pieces at the bottom (rows 1 and 2) and black pieces at the top (rows 7
Step 6: click (697, 870) [OK]\NI can see a chess board on the screen with white pieces at the bottom (rows 1 and 2) and black pieces at the top (rows 7
Step 7: click (697, 870) [OK]\NI can see a chess board on the screen with white pieces at the bottom (rows 1 and 2) and black pieces at the top (rows 7
Step 8: click (697, 870) [OK]\NI can see a chess board on the screen with white pieces at the bottom (rows 1 and 2) and black pieces at the top (rows 7
Step 9: click (697, 870) [OK]\NI can see a chess board on the screen. The white pieces are at the bottom (rows 1 and 2). I need to click on the e2 pawn
Step 10: click (697, 870) [OK]\NI can see a chess board on the screen with white pieces at the bottom (rows 1 and 2) and black pieces at the top (rows 7
Step 11: click (697, 870) [OK]\NI can see a chess board on the screen with white pieces at the bottom (rows 1 and 2) and black pieces at the top (rows 7
Step 12: click (700, 870) [OK]\NI can see a chess board on the screen with white pieces at the bottom (rows 1 and 2) and black pieces at the top (rows 7
Step 13: click (697, 870) [OK]\NI can see a chess board on the screen with white pieces at the bottom (rows 1 and 2) and black pieces at the top (rows 7
Step 14: find_and_click  [FAIL]\NI can see a chess board on the screen with white pieces at the bottom (rows 1 and 2) and black pieces at the top (rows 7
Step 15: click (700, 870) [OK]\NLooking at the chess board, I can see the white pieces are positioned at rows 1 and 2 at the bottom. The e2 pawn is the